[Music]
yo yo in the studio much track very rap
[Applause]
I'm in the 90s take a ride with beat
while we all recall
Wolpaw and prank phone calls bumpers for
you bowling ball would be hit them all
because this is New Jersey and stamp
late but still wake up early to get to
school your seat belt buckle to pokemon
cards taught me how to hustle and kiss
road orgy on their backpacks what is
asked me and my parents left home for
the evening googling a fan a slash
screen that passes me if I was a teen
basically of course I'm sure how does
the computer know when I was born a
generation formed by internet porn but
fucking back to high school romance is
all the way back just to the flu dances
Branson or Alec add something to prove I
was just a little kid with nothing to
lose and I was not cool but not
self-conscious they were teaching a
monster total bullshit that was totally
bonkers and bellman Crocker I was
actually noxious I was gonna fight in my
class and asshole the barely passed
specialist in your lounge I'll whup your
ass you know stories go it's all
happened a while ago but let's go back
here we go let's start the show
no Joe I didn't know we have skills you
chilled out with the time that you
killed how was online and on my damn car
making the question what you do with
your time picking it out my aunt's
basement video beans and go damn
patience tech skills and determination
trust with rage and frustration and I
got smarter and I grew richer and I felt
sharper as I move bigger culture than
iPhone kick it in the limo with the
screen off murmur who's sick I winner
winner in the green food chicken dinner
is an anachronism but I'm all atwitter
the picture chipper to better the
bidders well acquittal with a vigor to
the liver the record I tuned on and in
and dropped out not clear fight war for
food and self-doubt well I guess I
forgot how kid to a kid but I'm calling
my
I bought a fan I bought of Dan with an
energy drink in each hand tentatively
yelling fuck slams I would fire five in
my class and assholes barely
whole town traveling
your app and you know the stories go
this all happened a while ago but let's
go back now here we go
dim the lights turn the show what if you
want to besides my portrait death trap
for this nerds retreated in a second
Silicon Valley Haiti West but none of
it's what you expect that shows up in
your half Iraq tears me eyes with
Sonny's child not a grown man who works
in tech why would anybody buy this older
now and I still don't get it
your maturity in the house of cards back
by Benelli Shann rhetoric lockers and
unspoken code without again you stumble
through life with your dough stone
senators houses and cars and wives and
kids I live in a band like a damn
degenerate you have a house in a
swimming pool
look go rock climbing what a tool fuck
adulthood irony screw on the first in
high school I was older barely passed up
your ass and let's talk about where
teams have dropped out with nothing but
treats kill your stack dad just a patch
class well I take baths with dollar
bills - laughs horses corporation of kil
Jaeden we know what evocation but all
fractions
PlayStation and you know as stories go
this all happened a while ago but we're
here now 2014 wined it up and just let
it go think baffle you try to slow
blindfold on just feel the code don't
struggle transcend them use the fourth
let it go headspace that you're moving
boulders unbridled rage or child soldier
barren lifestyle barracks lifestyle
showers of a mine grow colder no more
dela banter with any word 24 not so
invincible anymore but I'm never gonna
die upload me and live on as information
forevermore I was thought of 5 in my
class an asshole II barely cast pull
time spent playing super smash in the
senior lounge I'll whup your ass if you
know his stories go I'm so glad to be
alive now throw a little get to be
around to see how the whole game plays
out I was about a 5 in my class and
asshole is barely past pull times
templates super smash in the senior
lounge I will whup your ass
did you know as stories go this one is
mine to control so hold on tight here we
go and watch close I've run this show
you